《猛鬼街2：弗莱迪的复仇》
慢慢来
Hey, take it easy.
再见
See you.
关小声点
Turn it down.
- 那个怪胎? - 我是说真的
- Ew, that geek? - I'm serious.
不可能  我才不在乎
No way, I don't care.
不可能  你骗人
No way, you're such a liar.
- 不知道  他在我们后面  - 什么
- I don't know, he's right behind us. - What?
不可能
No way.
他是你的了  起码他还活着
That one's for you. He's a live one.
他才是你的  我家快到了
Uh-uh, he's yours. Oh, we're coming to my house.
嘿  司机  嘿
Hey, driver. Hey!
司机  我要在那一站下车
Hey, driver, that was my stop.
Driver, that was my stop.
司机  发生了什么事
Driver, what's going on?
我们要去哪里
Where are we going?
让我们下车  快点
Let us out. Come on.
- 司机  - 你在做什么
- Driver? - What are you doing?
快停车
Stop it!
停车
Stop!
求求你快停车
Please. Please stop.
- 发生了什么事  - 不知道
- What's happening? - I don't know.
天啊
Oh, my God.
发生了什么事
What's going on?
天啊
Oh, my God.
天啊  我们被困在这里了
Oh, my God. We're stuck here.
天啊  这是怎么一回事
Oh, my God! What is this?
那是什么东西
What's that?
- 那是什么东西  - 天啊  是他  快点
- What is it? - Oh, my God, it's him! Come on!
天啊
Oh, my God!
快打开车门  他来了
Open this thing. He's coming!
- 不要  - 天啊
- No! - God!
- 天啊  快点  - 救救我们
- Oh, my God, come on! - Save us!
打开车门
Get the door.
妈妈  为什么杰西不能跟其他人一样醒来
Mommy, why can't Jesse wake up like everybody else?
甜心  他没事的
Oh, honey, he's all right.
他只是做了恶梦
He's just having a bad dream.
谢谢
Mm. Thank you.
早安  甜心
Good morning, honey.
妈
Hi, Ma.
又有两箱  哈利路亚
Well, two more. Hallelujah.
我要你在今晚之前把房间收拾好  小子
I want that room unpacked by tonight, young man.
好啦  爸  我跟你保证
Okay, Dad. I promise.
我不要再听你的保证  杰西
I don't want any more promises, Jesse.
我要你把房间打扫干净  好吗
I want that room cleaned up, okay?
好啦  我会打扫的
All right, I'll get on it.
不行
No.
- 安琪  你想做什么  - 我要找富曼指偶
- Angie, what are you up to? - I'm trying to get the Fuman fingers.
- 要吃点蛋吗  - 不要
- Want some eggs? - No.
杰西  你没事吧
Jesse, are you okay?
房间好热  我睡不好
It's so hot up there, I'm having trouble sleeping.
我知道  肯  我要你打电话找人来修空调
I know. Ken, I wish you'd call somebody and have the air conditioning.
空调没坏  妈妈
There's absolutely nothing wrong with that air conditioning, mom.
只是要加冷媒
Just needs a shot of Freon.
- 找到了  - 不会吧
- Here they are. - Oh, no.
拜托  爸  你又想自己修理东西了
Come on, Dad, you're not trying to fix something again.
没有人喜欢多嘴的人  儿子
Nobody likes a smart ass, buddy boy.
看吧
Look.
谁来了
Who's that?
是莉莎
It's Lisa.
我得去上学了
I gotta get to school.
莉莎是谁
Whoa, whoa. Who's Lisa?
Who is Lisa?
快吃蛋吧  亲爱的
Just eat your eggs, dear.
- 嗨  - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
你不用钥匙吗
Don't you ever use a key?
为什么
Why?
有人会偷你的车吧
Somebody could steal your car, couldn't they?
这辆破车
The deadly dinosaur?
好球
Strike.
葛莱帝  加油  你打得中的
Grady, come on, you can hit this stuff.
准备好了吗  女孩们
You ready, girls?
很不错
That was very good.
好好投
Easy out.
轻松打
Easy hit. Easy hit.
- 哈! - 好球
- Ha! - Strike.
他已经离开那里
Get him out of there already.
那一球不合我胃口  好吗  饶了我吧
Didn't feel right, okay? Give me a break.
你们做了吗  莉莎
So you getting any yet, Lise?
凯丽  我只是搭他便车上学
Kerry, he's my ride to school, okay?
加油  加油
Put it out. Put it out.
- 你没事吧  - 没事
- You all right? - Yeah.
- You okay there? - Yeah.
打得好  打得好
Good shot, good shot.
你没事吧
You okay?
我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
下次专心一点
Well, pay attention next time.
注意看球
Very heads-up play.
接得可真好啊  华许
Nice catch, Walsh.
来吧  快一点
Come on, come on. Let's go.
加油  米区
Come on, Mitch.
好啊
All right!
快点
Come on.
触杀他
Knock him down.
你出局了
You're out.
注意看球  葛莱帝
Heads up play, Grady.
- 帅啊  - 帅啊
- All right! - All right!
屁股还蛮漂亮的
Nice ass.
- 来吧  - 给他好看
- Come on! - Get him!
加油  打扁他
Come on, slug him!
快点  打扁他
Go on, slug him!
打扁他  快点
Slug him. Come on, slug him!
打扁他
Slug him!
- 史奈德来了  - 小心
- Here comes Schneider. - Watch out.
- 你可以打赢他的  加油  - 让开
- You can get him, come on! - Get out of my way.
- 加油  - 好了  两个浑虫
- Come on. - Okay, dirtballs.
加油
Come on.
快就位
Assume the position.
再见  教练
See you around, coach.
兄弟  冷静点
Hey, man, chill out, dude.
闭嘴
Shut up, dude.
来吧
Come on. Come on.
你觉得他还要处罚我们多久
How much longer do you think he's gonna keep us out here?
有可能是一整夜
It could be all night.
那家伙最爱搞这套了
The guy gets his rocks off like this.
他喜欢到城里泡变装酒吧
Hangs around queer S&M joints downtown.
他喜欢你这样的帅小子
He likes pretty boys like you.
别闹了
Get out of here.
你跟每天搭你便车上学的美女  又是怎么一回事
What about you and that babe you've been cruising to school with every day?
她怎么了
What about her?
你跟她上了吗
Are you mounting her nightly or what?
喂  葛莱帝  你对我有意见吗
Look, Grady, you got some problem with me?
当然没有
No, bro.
我只是在消磨时间
Just killing time.
天啊  那真是恶心
Oh, God, that's gross.
好了  浑虫  快去洗澡
Okay, dirtballs, hit the shower.
你住在这附近吗
So you live around here or what?
对  我爸妈在榆树街买了间房子
Yeah, my parents just bought a place on Elm Street.
榆树街
Elm Street?
你们不会是搬到那间有铁窗的白色大房子吧
You moved into that big white house with bars in the window?
对啊  怎么了
Yeah, what about it?
该死  你可以跟你爸说他超勇敢的
Shit. You can tell your old man he's a real chump.
你在胡说什么  葛莱帝
What are you talking about now, Grady?
以前有个女孩被她妈妈关在那里面  她发疯了
Some chick was locked in there by her mother and she went crazy.
她看到她男朋友在对街被一个疯子杀了
She watched her boyfriend get butchered across the street by some maniac.
你在胡说八道  葛莱帝
You're full of shit, Grady.
爸
Dad?
Dad!
救命啊
Help!
现在你爸爸救不了你
Daddy can't help you now.
我需要你  杰西
I need you, Jesse.
我们有很特别的事要做  就你跟我
We've got special work to do here, you and me.
你有身体
You've got the body...
我有脑袋
...I've got the brain.
杰西
Jess?
Jesse.
- 你觉得我们该打电话给医生吗  - 不
- Do you think we should call the doctor? - No.
不  我没事
No, I'm fine.
我只是做了恶梦  好吗
It's just a bad dream, okay?
好吧
Yeah.
快睡吧
Yeah, go to sleep.
我们来复习一下
So to review.
固体废弃物  胃膜无法吸收的养分
The solid wastes, those nutrients not absorbed in the lining of the stomach...
还有大肠跟小肠
...the large intestine, the small intestine...
主要消化道无法吸收的会从结肠排出来
...and the elementary canal are passed out through the colon.
液态养分会经过精密的过滤系统
Liquid nutrients are then carried through an elaborate system of filtering...
包括胰脏  肝脏跟胆囊
...aided by the pancreas, liver and gall bladder...
累积在膀胱里  稍后再排出
...or collected in the bladder to be expelled at a later time.
整个过程不断地进行
And this entire process is kept moving...
透过循环系统  中心就是
...through the circulatory system, the center of which is...
心脏
...the heart.
- 耶! - 哎呀
- Yeah! - Ew.
分成四个空间
Four chambers.
就跟人类的心脏一样
Just like the human heart, really.
从身体到右心耳  再到右心室
From the body to the right auricle, to the right ventricle...
从肺动脉流到肺脏
...and out the pulmonary arteries to the lungs.
交换二氧化碳及氧气
There it trades off carbon dioxide for oxygen.
吐出二氧化碳  含氧的血液继续
Carbon dioxide is exhaled and the oxygenated blood continues to....
流入左心耳  经过左心室流到
Into the left auricle through the left ventricle passing out of the....
不
No!
如果你要跟动物玩  华许先生  请加入马戏团
If you wanna play with animals, Mr. Walsh, join the circus.
莉莎  甜心  有个叫杰西的打电话给你
Lisa, sweetheart, there's a Jesse on the phone.
好的  谢谢你  妈妈
Okay. Thanks, Mom.
杰西
Jesse?
嗨
Hi.
国内新闻方面
On the national front....
- 你要去哪里  杰西  - 只是出去一下
- Where are you going, Jess? - Just out for a little while.
我要你把房间整理好
I told you I want that room unpacked.
- 我只是出去一  两个小时  - 不行
- I'm just going out for an hour or two. - No.
上楼
Upstairs.
快点  儿子
Right now, son.
快点
Right now.
你懂得如何爱我
Ooh, you know how to love me, yeah
今晚我们什么时候做爱
When we make love tonight?
满意了吧  爸
How do you like that, Dad?
我是多么的需要你  宝贝
I need you so bad, baby
这是属于你的地方
This is where you belong.
别让我等得太久
Don't make me wait too long.
不
No
一整晚
All night long.
抱着我  宝贝  让我发疯
Hold me, baby, Drive me crazy.
触摸我一整夜
Touch me all night long
让我爱你  亲吻  拥抱你
Make me love you Kiss and hug you.
杰西
Jesse.
触摸我一整夜
Touch me all night long
你是我的糖果人
You're my candy man.
我不打扰你们两个了
Ha. I'll, uh...I'll leave the two of you alone.
失陪了
Excuse me.
我跟她说你邀请我过来
I told her you invited me over.
我也许该先打电话过来
I guess maybe I should have called.
不  真的没关系
No. Ha, ha. It's fine, really.
我只是在打扫房间
I mean, I was just cleaning my room.
我知道
I know.
我想你需要帮忙
I figured you might like some help.
这个要放哪里
Where does this go?
毛衣放在衣橱里吗
Um.... Do your sweaters go in the closet?
这是什么
What's this?
不知道  看起来像是日记
I don't know. Looks like a diary to me.
来看一下吧
Let's see.
"南茜汤普森  榆树街1428号"
"Nancy Thompson. 1428 Elm Street."
就是这里
That's right here.
你知道吗  这是五年前的日记
Hey, you know, this thing is five years old.
- 你认识她吗  - 不认识  那时我还没有搬过来
- You know her? - Uh-uh. No. Before my time.
等一下  你听这一段
Wait, listen to this.
"有时我躺在床上
"Sometimes when I'm lying here in bed...
可以看到对面的葛兰在房间  准备要上床睡觉
...I can see Glen in his window across the way getting ready for bed.
他的身材健壮光滑
His body is slim and smooth...
我知道我不该看他  但我的心是渴望他的
...and I know I shouldn't watch him but that part of me that wants him...
所以我盯着他看
...forces me to.
那时的我如此软弱
That's when I wea.
那时我想去找他"
That's when I wanna go to him."
- 我能看一下吗 - 嗯嗯
- Can I see that? - Mm-hm.
"3月15日
"March 15th.
晚上他来找我
He comes to me at night.
可怕  丑陋  肮脏  跟我一起躺在床上
Horrible, ugly, dirty, under the sheets with me.
用他的钢爪撕开我的睡衣
Tearing at my nightgown with his steel claws.
他叫做佛莱迪
His name is Fred...
他一直想带我去锅炉室
...and he keeps trying to take me to the boiler room.
他想杀了我"
He wants to kill me."
怎么了
What is it?
"提娜死了"
"Tina is dead."
杰西  你没事吧
Jesse, are you okay?
葛莱帝跟我提过这件事
It's just something that Grady said to me.
以前住在这里的女孩
About the that used to live here?
她看到住在对面的男朋友被杀  因此发疯了
How she went crazy when she saw her boyfriend get murdered across the street.
啊
Ugh.
快点  杰西
Go ahead, Jesse.
试试看大小合不合适
Try it on for size.
帮我杀人
Kill for me.
我像是在梦游一样
It was kind of like I was sleepwalking.
或许你有通灵的超能力
Maybe you were having a premonition or something, you know.
就像那些帮助警方破案  寻找失踪人口的人
Like the guys who help police solve crimes and find missing people.
你以前会这样吗
Ever have anything like this happen before?
不  从来没有
Nope. Never.
- 你真的认为是那样  - 我不知道
- You think that's what it is? - I don't know.
能让我看一下日记吗
Can I see the diary for a little while?
谢谢
Thanks.
- 两位好  - 凯丽
- Hi, guys. - Hi, Kerry.
我收到你的周末派对邀请函了
I got your invitation for the party this weed.
会有帅哥来吗
Any cute guys gonna be there?
全都是帅哥
All of them. Ha, ha.
这次也是你爸当流行音乐节目主持人吗
Is your dad gonna be the DJ again?
- 妈这次会把他关在楼上  - 太棒了
- Mom is gonna keep him upstairs this time. - Oh, good.
我上次办派对
Last party I had...
我爸坚持整晚要播班尼古德曼的歌
...my Dad insisted on playing Benny Goodman records all night.
- 待会儿见  好吗  - 好的
- Well, I'll see you later, okay? - Okay.
葛莱帝  你记得你做过的梦吗
Hey, Grady, do you remember your dreams?
我只记得春梦
Only the wet ones.
别说话
No talking.
葛莱帝
Hey, Grady.
史奈德不该在最后一局把你换下来
You know, Schneider shouldn't have called you out on that last play.
对  今天史奈德是个王八蛋
Yeah, well, Schneider has got a stick up his ass today.
史奈德一直都是个王八蛋
Schneider's always got a stick up his ass.
两个浑虫  你们好
Hello, dirtballs.
- 这里真的很热  - 对  宝贝
- Ugh. It is so hot in here. - Yeah, babe.
我看一下自动调温器
Let me Iook at the thermostat.
天啊  这里热得跟烤箱一样
My God, it is hot as an oven in here.
小鸟在睡觉
Shh. The birds are sleeping.
雪若  这里是摄氏36度
Cheryl, it's 97 degrees in here.
该死
Damn it. Ow!
安琪拉  小心
Angela, watch out.
小心  杰西
Watch out, Jesse.
- 啊  - 肯  你没事吧
- Ah! - Ken,are you all right?
该死的鸟  小心  安琪拉  快闪开
Damn bird. Look out, Angela, get out.
小心  杰西
Look out, Jesse.
- 来吧  - 小心  安琪拉
- Come on. - Look out, Angela.
杰西  快让开
Jesse, get out of here.
雪若
Cheryl.
你在做什么  杰西  帮我把这玩意儿移开
What are you doing, Jesse? Help me move this thing.
- 这不是瓦斯漏气  - 别跟我说不是瓦斯漏气
- It isn't the gas. - Don't tell me it's not the gas.
你妈觉得她闻到瓦斯味
Your mother thought she smelled gas.
我以为我闻到了  我不确定
Well, I thought I did, I wasn't sure.
好吧  怎么了  这是狂鸟病吗
All right, so, what is it, bird rabies?
- 一定是你买的饲料有问题  - 拜托  肯  真的
- It's that seed you've been buying. - Please, really.
不  有可能  这一定有合理的解释
No, it could be. Got to be a rational explanation.
动物不会没理由突然自爆  对吧
Animals don't explode into flames for no reason, do they?
- 没错  - 好吧
- That's right. - All right.
绝对不是瓦斯漏气
Well, it's sure not a leaky gas pipe.
- 你没事吧  - 没事
- You all right? - Oh, it's all right.
这是你在搞鬼  对吧
You set this whole thing up, didn't you?
你在胡说什么
What are you talking about?
你知道我在说什么  你用了什么  爆竹吗
You know what I'm talking about. What did you use, firecrackers?
你知道他做了什么  他用了冲天炮
You know what he did, he used a goddamn cherry bomb.
- 少来  - 他就是那么做的
- Stop it. - That's what he did.
喂  你不能那样子跟我说话
Look, you can't talk to me like that.
- 杰西  给我回来  - 肯
- Jesse, come back. - Ken.
- 给我回来  杰西  - 别说了  你真的很荒谬
- Come back, Jesse! - Stop it, you're being ridiculous.
- 好了  别说了  - 杰西
- Now come on, stop it. - Jesse!
该死
Shit.
天啊
Oh, jeez.
- 不知道  他一直想  - 别碰我
- I don't know, he always wants to. - Don't touch me.
能给我一杯啤酒吗  谢谢
Can I have a beer, please?
去冲个澡吧
Hit the shower.
不  不  不
No, no, no! No!
不
No, no!
不  该死
No, goddamn it, no!
不
No!
No, no.
不
No!
天啊
Oh, boy.
晚安  这是你们的儿子吗
Good evening, uh, does this belong to you?
对  他是我儿子
Uh, yes, sir, he's my son.
我们发现他在公路上游荡
We found him out on the highway wandering around.
没穿衣服
He was naked.
我建议你们管好他
I'd keep a short leash on him if I were you.
谢谢你  警官
Thank you, officer.
杰西  进来  快点
Jesse, come here, come.
嘿
Hey, hey.
过来
Come here.
我有两个问题
Two questions.
你回答问题  大家都能去睡  好吗
You answer them and we can all go to bed, all right?
你吃了什么药  儿子
What are you taking, son?
是谁给你药
Who are you getting it from?
我没有嗑药
I'm not taking drugs.
- 妈  我要睡了  - 对  来吧
- Mom, I wanna go to bed. - Yeah, come on.
那只是个我得自己解决的问题
It's just a problem I have to work out on my own.
- 但有事让你感到困扰  - 妈
- But something's bothering you. - Mom.
我们只是很担心你  杰西
We're just concerned about you, Jesse.
- 我没事  别烦我  - 我们
- I'm fine, just leave me alone. - Can't...
- 我们不能谈一谈吗  - 不行
- Can't we at least talk about it? - No.
他需要专家帮忙  我想我们该送他去看心理医生
He needs professional help. I think we have to take him to a psychiatrist.
少来了  雪若  你疯了  那么做有什么好处
Come on, Cheryl, you're out of your gourd. What will that do?
我不知道  他需要帮助  我们不知道怎么帮他
I don't know. He needs help and we don't know how to give it.
- 别闹了  雪若  - 你听到了吗
- Oh, come on, Cheryl. - Are you hearing me?
- 那孩子有麻烦  - 不  他没有麻烦
- That boy's in trouble. - No, he's not in trouble.
那孩子需要被好好管教一顿
What that boy needs is a good goddamn kick in the butt.
他只需要那样
That's what he needs.
我知道他需要什么  他需要去戒毒
I'll tell you what he needs. He needs a methadone clinic.
发生了什么事
What's happening?
所有的学生回到教室
I want all you back to your classes....
别担心
Don't worry about what....
别担心  让他们做他们的工作  好吗
Just don't worry about it. Let them do their work, all right?
兄弟  你跑到哪里去了
Yo, man, where have you been?
- 昨晚史奈德被杀了  - 天啊
- Schneider got wasted last night. - Oh, my God.
他一定是在加班  有个疯子把他当香肠开肠剖肚
He must have been working late. Some maniac sliced him like a kielbasa.
在洗澡间攻击他  到处都是血脚印
Hacked him in the shower. Got bloody footprints all over the place.
请退到封锁线后面
COPStand back from the line, please.
帮我杀人
Kill for me.
一  二
One, two
佛莱迪来找你了
Freddy's coming for you
三  四
Three, four
你最好锁上门
Better lock your door
五  六
Five, six
拿起你的十字架
Grab your crucifix
- 早安  杰西  - 早安
- Morning, Jess. - Morning.
爸  他们为什么花了五年时间  才把房子卖掉
Dad, how come it took them five years to sell this house?
不知道
Oh, I don't know.
我想是价钱一直无法让他们满意吧
They just couldn't get the right price, I suppose.
你不知道对面发生过命案吗
Didn't know about the murder across the street?
住在这里的女孩目睹整个过程  后来发疯了
The that lived here that saw the whole thing.
他们跟我提过  可是我…
They told me something about it, yeah, but I...
- 你是说你早就知道这件…  - 拜托  雪若
- You knew something about this... - Come on, Cheryl.
你觉得我们怎么会  谈到这么低的价钱  甜心
How do you think we got such a good deal here, hon?
他们有跟你说那女孩疯了吗
Did they tell you that that lost her mind?
她妈妈在客厅自杀
And her mother killed herself in our living room?
- 什么  - 他们有跟你说吗
- What? - Did they tell you that?
妈  我好害怕
Mom, I'm scared.
- 过来  - 甜心  没事的
- Come here. - Oh, honey, it's all right.
爸跟杰西只是在闹着玩
Daddy and Jesse are just pretending, that's all.
我想我们不该在这里讨论这件事
I don't think this is something we should discuss.
看吧  我不想听这件事  杰西
See? Don't wanna hear one more word about it.
真的没事  我是说  这间房子没问题
There's absolutely nothing, I mean nothing, wrong with this house.
好了
Come on.
有东西烧焦了吗
Is something burning?
天啊
Good Lord.
那是我看过最疯狂的事
It's the craziest damn thing I've ever seen.
你看  雪若
Look here, Cheryl.
插头根本没插上
It wasn't even plugged in.
杰西  你不能为史奈德的死自责
Jesse, you can't blame yourself for what happened to Schneider.
你梦到不代表你是凶手
And just because you dreamt it doesn't mean you did it.
- 我们要去哪里  - 这边左转
- Where are we going? - Veer left over here.
听着  我真的觉得这是你的想像
Look, I really think this is all in your mind, you know...
你应该是接收到灵界讯息
...Iike you're picking up some psychic signals.
哇  这是什么地方
Wow, what is this place?
还记得日记的内容吗
Do you remember in the diary?
南茜说她发现自己到了锅炉室
When Nancy said she kept finding herself in a boiler room?
佛莱迪克格在这里工作  这是老发电厂
Well, Fred Krueger worked here. It's an old power plant.
- 拿去吧  - 这是什么
- Here. - What is all this?
我调查了一下我们的朋友  佛莱迪克格
I did some reading on our friend, Fred Krueger.
- 这里废弃多久了  - 非常久
- How long has it been closed down? - A long time.
来吧
Come on.
天啊
Jesus.
佛莱迪克格绑架了二十个孩子
Fred Krueger kidnapped 20 kids...
将他们带到这里杀害
...and brought them here and killed them.
- 你有感觉了吗  - 你是什么意思
- Do you feel anything? - What do you mean?
不知道  我想你应该会有感应
I don't know. I thought you might be able to make a connection or something.
- 我觉得自己是个混蛋  - 专心点
- I feel like a jerk. - Shh. Just concentrate.
你有感觉吗
Do you feel anything?
嗯
Uh, uh.
醒一醒  小女孩
Wake up, little .
几点了
What time is it?
很晚了  继续睡吧
It's late, go back to sleep.
早安  甜心  你睡得好吗
Morning, honey. Did you sleep okay?
还不错
Yeah, fine.
很好  你的气色好多了
Good. You're looking better.
你又做恶梦了  对不对
You had another nightmare, didn't you?
对  昨晚我很不好受
Yes, I had a bad night.
你要谈一谈吗
Do you wanna talk about it?
我爸以为我嗑药
My dad thinks I'm on drugs.
我妈以为我疯了
My mom thinks I'm crazy.
现在我不知道是否该同意她的看法
And you know, at this point, I don't know if I don't agree with her.
杰西是怎么了  他一副阴阳怪气的模样
Hey, what's wrong with Jesse? He seems kind of freaked out.
要一起去看电影或去玩吗
Hey, wanna go to a movie or something, hang out?
或许可以忘了这些事  大家一起去吃披萨
Maybe get these things off your mind. Get a pizza or something.
你们好
Hey, guys.
朗尼
Hi, Ronnie.
- 明晚你要去莉莎家吗  - 没办法
- You going to Lisa's house tomorrow night? - No.
- 不行  我被禁足了  - 怎么会
- I can't, I'm grounded. - How come?
我把我奶奶推下楼
I threw my grandmother down a flight of stairs.
杰西
Jesse.
杰西  我想你该吃点东西
Jesse, I think you should eat something.
- 我不饿  - 我希望你能跟我谈一谈
- I'm not hungry. - I wish you would talk to me.
我们可以一起想办法
You know, we can figure it out. We can figure it out together.
没什么可想的
There is nothing to figure out.
我不知道你干嘛  跟这家伙浪费时间
I don't know why you're wasting your time.
- 他是个变态  - 闭嘴  葛莱帝
- He's a basket case. - Shut up, Grady.
你要我闭嘴  好  我闭嘴  没问题
Want me to shut up? Fine, I'll shut up, no problem.
待会儿不见  兄弟
See you around, buddy.
拿去吧
Here you are.
- 好啊  - 漂亮
- Hey. - All right.
喂  别闹了
Hey, now cut that out.
我来处理
I've got it.
甜心  这派对很好玩
But, sweetheart, it's a nice party.
来吧  健美先生  该睡了
Come on, Skinny, it's time for bed.
交给你了  小子
You're in charge, hotshot.
小姐  12点半结束  别拖延
Twelve-thirty, miss, no later.
- 12点半  - 好好玩
- Twelve-thirty. - Have a nice time.
嗨
Hi.
杰西是怎么了
What's the matter with Jesse?
我不知道
I don't know.
- 杰西  - 我马上出去
- Jesse? - I'll be out in a second.
我能进去跟你谈吗
Can I please come in and talk to you?
我想离开了  我玩不起来
Listen, I'm gonna leave. I'm not into this.
对不起
I'm sorry.
杰西  你为什么不跟我谈
Jesse, why won't you talk to me?
- 你能不能别来烦我  - 你太不公平了
- Will you just leave me alone? - You're not being fair.
我想帮你
I wanna help you.
你要怎么帮我
How can you help me?
你能为我做什么
What are you gonna do for me?
真的  我觉得我快疯了
Look, I feel like I'm losing my mind.
我不要你看到我崩溃
And I don't want you to watch me fall apart.
我害怕睡着
I'm afraid to go to sleep.
醒着的时候也害怕
I'm afraid to stay awake.
我毁了你的派对
I'm ruining your party.
- 他们会将我送走  - 好了  别那么说
- They're gonna take me away. - Come on, don't say that.
听着  有必要的话  我们整晚都不睡
Listen, we'll stay up all night if we have to.
我不会让你出事的
I'm not gonna let anything happen to you.
来吧  准备好就可以了
Come on, any second now, any second.
太棒了  派对时间
Yeah, party time.
我来放音乐
I got the music.
我想告诉你我的感觉
I wanna tell you exactly how I feel.
- 他们在搞什么  - 艾迪  他们只是孩子
- What the hell are they doing down there? - Oh, Eddie, they're kids.
我知道他们只是孩子  我得休息一下
I know they're kids. I gotta get some rest.
现在你要离开  是我承认的时候了
Now that you're leaving. It's time that I confess.
计划我们相爱的方式
The way we planned our love together.
有时做多与做少一样
Sometimes doing more is less.
从耳语变作尖叫  现在我知道这意味着什么
From a whisper to a scream. Now I know just what it means.
从耳语变作尖叫声  我说过我爱你
From a whisper to a scream. I said I love you.
从耳语变作尖叫  现在我知道这意味着什么
From a whisper to a scream. Now I know just what it means.
昨天你还只属于我  今天你爱上新欢
Yesterday you were only mine. Today you're loving somebody new.
怎么了
What is it?
杰西  怎么了
Jesse, what's wrong?
天啊  你差点没吓死我
Jesus Christ, you scared the shit out of me, man.
你在做什么
Hey, what are you doing?
喂  你跑到我的房间做什么
Hey, what the fuck are you doing in my room?
听着  我惹上大麻烦了
Listen, I'm in trouble.
今晚我需要你收容我
I need you to let me stay here tonight.
你疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
我不知道
I don't know.
天啊
Oh, man.
你何不回家吃瓶安眠药
Why don't you just go home and take a bottle of sleeping pills?
我杀了史奈德
I killed Schneider.
什么
You what?
但动手的人不是我  懂吗
Only it wasn't me, see?
是我心里的那股力量
There's something inside of me.
昨晚它要我进我妹的房间
And last night it made me go to my sister's room.
今晚我跟莉莎在泳池小屋  我又感觉到那股力量了
And tonight with Lisa in the cabana it started to happen again.
我觉得你真的疯了  兄弟
I think you are seriously losing it, bro.
我很害怕  葛莱帝
I'm scared, Grady.
有股力量想侵入我的身体
Something is trying to get inside my body.
对  她是女生  她在泳池小屋等你
Yeah, she's female, she's waiting for you in the cabana.
你却要跟我睡
And you wanna sleep with me.
听着  我不在乎你相不相信我
Look, I don't care if you believe me or not.
嘿  我相信你
Hey, I believe you.
你做了可怕的恶梦  好吗
You've had some scary dreams, okay?
不
No.
我不知道
I don't know.
我被搞糊涂了
I'm all messed up.
那有什么差别
What difference does it make?
我有麻烦  我需要你帮我
I'm in trouble. And I need you to help me.
好吗
Okay?
好吧  你要我怎么做
All right, man. What do you want me to do?
看好我
Just watch me.
如果真的出事
And if anything starts to happen...
如果我开始怪怪的  看起来像是做了怪梦
...if I start to act weird, start dreaming weird...
或是我想离开这里  你得阻止我
...or try to walk out of here, you gotta stop me.
不管是打昏我还是怎么样  千万别让我离开
I don't care if you have to hit me over the head, just don't let me leave.
葛莱帝
And, Grady...
别睡着了
...don't fall asleep.
要吃热狗吗
Hot dog?
快回水里
Come back in the water.
我在忙  好吗
I'm busy, okay?
我不知道  凯丽  我觉得我该去看他
I don't know, Kerry. I feel like I should go see him.
但我不能丢下派对不管
But I can't just leave the party.
管他的派对
Fuck the party.
去找他吧
Go see him.
对
Yeah.
离开死人国度  拿着火把
Leaving the land of the dead, and with Torch...
我要你见见路易
I want you to meet Louie...
现在我看到
And now I see the...
看吧  孩子  你太厉害了
See, kid, you're a dog.
你把情况处理得很好
You sure handled that situation...
把绳子丢过来给我  那变成无底洞了
Throw me a line. That changes into a bottomless pit!
好好睡吧  兄弟
Sweet dreams, pal.
- 葛莱帝  - 怎么
- Grady. - What?
我又有感觉了
It's starting to happen again.
天啊
Jesus.
兄弟
Hey, man.
你到底是怎么了
What the fuck's wrong with you, dude?
要死了
Shit.
天啊
Oh, my God.
爸
Dad!
爸  快开门
Dad, open the door!
爸
Dad!
不
No!
爸
Dad! Dad!
Dad!
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
爸  快开门
Dad, open the door! Dad!
爸
Dad!
朗
Ron.
朗  怎么了
Ron, what is it?
爸
Dad!
爸  快开门
Ron, open the door!
朗  你没事吧
Ron, are you all right?
朗  我是你爸  快开门
Ron, this is your father, open this door!
不  不
No! No!
- 不  - 朗
- No! - Ron!
朗  快开门
Ron, open it up! Ron!
朗
MRS.
快找人帮忙
MR. . Get help!
不
No.
你这个大混蛋
You son of a bitch!
你杀了他
You killed him!
不
No!
里面有人吗  快开门
Somebody in there? Open up.
门锁住了  把门撞开
It's locked. Break it down.
带走一朵玫瑰
Take a rose.
称之为悲伤
Call it sorrow.
但是名不符实
But it's a rose by any other name.
杰西  天啊  发生了什么事
Jesse, my God, what happened?
我杀了他  我杀了他
I killed him. I killed him.
杰西  天啊  你受伤了  发生了什么事
Jesse, my God, you're hurt. What happened?
我  杀了葛莱帝
I...I killed Grady.
我杀了葛莱帝
I killed Grady.
莉莎  我杀了史奈德
Lisa, I killed Schneider.
不  天啊
Oh, no, my God.
我好害怕
I'm so scared.
杰西  你在胡说什么
Jesse, what are you talking about?
他在我的身体里
He's inside me.
- 我好害怕  - 杰西  是谁对你这么做
- I'm scared. - Jesse, who is doing this to you?
佛莱迪克格
Fred Krueger.
他在我的身体里  他还想再度控制我
He's inside me, and he wants to take me again.
不  不
No. No.
杰西
Jesse.
杰西  这是不可能的
Jesse, this is not happening.
一定是你受了太大的刺激  史奈德  日记  手套
It's got to be everything you've ta in. Uh, Schneider the diary, the glove.
你被搞糊涂了
Only it's all mixed up...
天啊  我该怎么做你才会相信我
Christ, what do I have to do to make you understand me?
昨晚他想逼我杀死我妹妹
Last night he made me try to kill my sister.
我手上沾着血
I've got blood on my hands.
他控制了我
He owns me.
拜托谁把热水器关了
Hey, could somebody turn down the heat in the pool?
发生了什么事
What's going on?
该死
Shit.
- 洛基  - 我们的英雄
- Hey, Rocky. - Our hero.
杰西
Jesse.
来吧  我要你听一下这个
Come on, I just want you to listen to this.
这是南茜的日记最后一页
It's something Nancy said in the last page of her diary.
听着
Listen.
"他就是邪恶本身
"He is evil itself.
我知道是我带他来到我的世界
I know now that I brought him into my world.
我们都一样
We all did.
给了他需要的能量
Gave him all the energy he needed.
他只需要听到我们尖叫"
Our were all he needed."
莉莎吗
Lisa?
杰西  她没疯  这一切真的发生过
Jesse, she wasn't crazy. All this really happened.
你可以抵抗他
You can fight him.
天啊  他回来了
Oh, God, he's coming back.
- 快离开这里  莉莎  - 杰西  抵抗他
- Get out of here, Lisa. - Jesse, fight him.
我没办法
I can't.
抵抗到底  杰西
Fight it, Jesse.
你创造了他  你也可以毁了他
You created him, you can destroy him.
莉莎  快开门
Lisa, open this door.
他靠你的恐惧而活
He is living off of your fear.
- 杰西  抵抗他  - 我没办法
- Jesse, fight him. - I can't!
不  你可以的
Yes, you can.
抵抗他
Fight him.
你不怕他  他根本不存在
You are not afraid of him.
- 他根本不存在  - 不
- He doesn't even exist. - No!
天啊
Oh, my God.
杰西
Jesse?
他不能抵抗我  我就在这里
He can't fight me. I'm here.
不
No, no!
救命啊
Help!
不
No!
杰西
Jesse!
救命啊
Help!
老天爷
Oh, my God!
不
No!
不要
Don't.
不
No!
- 太热了  - 发生了什么事
- It's gotten a little hot. - What's going on in there?
天啊
My God!
杰西  帮帮我
Jesse, help.
杰西不存在
There is no Jesse.
现在我就是杰西
I'm Jesse now.
离我远一点
Get away from me!
杀了我  莉莎
Kill me, Lisa.
求求你  杀了我
Please, kill me.
快点  莉莎  杀了他
Come on, Lisa, kill him.
杀了他
Kill him.
我爱你  莉莎
I love you, Lisa.
不
No.
天啊
Oh, God.
帮帮我  拜托
Help, please.
拜托
PIease.
不
No.
我爱你  莉莎
I love you, Lisa.
杰西  帮帮我
Jesse, help.
大家都没事吧
Hey, is everybody okay?
我不知道
Search me.
发生了什么事
What's going on?
等一下  等一下
Wait a minute! Wait!
好烫
Ah! It's hot.
莉莎  莉莎
Lisa. Lisa.
莉莎  天啊  你没事吧
Lisa. Oh, my God, are you all right?
妈妈
Mommy.
快带她离开这里
Get her out of here!
- 快离开这里  - 好啦
- Get out of here! - All right.
嘿
Hey.
冷静点  好吗
Just calm down, all right?
放轻松
Relax.
对  一定会没事的
Yeah. It's gonna be all right.
没有人会伤害你
Nobody's gonna hurt you.
告诉我们你要什么  好吗
Just tell us what you want, all right?
好吧  我是来帮你的
Okay, I'm here to help you.
你先帮帮自己吧  混蛋
Help yourself, fucker.
现在你们都是我的孩子
You are all my children now.
该死
Oh, shit.
不  不要
No! Don't.
你在做什么
What the hell are you doing?
他到哪里去了
Where did he go?
到我这边来  莉莎
Come to me, Lisa.
杰西  我知道你还在
Jesse, I know you're in there.
- 阻止他  - 不  杰西死了
- Stop him. - No, no, no, Jesse's dead.
杰西
Jesse.
莉莎
Lisa.
我爱你  杰西
I love you, Jesse.
莉莎
Lisa.
回到我身边  莉莎
Come back to me, Lisa.
我才不怕你
I am not afraid of you.
他在那里面  把他还给我
He's in there and I want him back.
我要把他从你手上抢回来
I'm gonna take him away from you.
你会直接下地狱去  大混蛋
And you are gonna go straight back to hell, you son of a bitch!
不  杰西死了
No, Jesse's dead.
回到我身边  杰西
Come back to me, Jesse.
我爱你
I love you.
回到我身边
Come back to me.
他死了
He's dead.
他无法控制你  杰西
He can't hold you, Jesse.
他失去控制了
He's losing his grip.
你可以逃出来的
You can get out.
他会跟我一起死
He'll die with me.
他会跟我们两个一起死
He'll die with both of us.
莉莎  莉莎
Lisa! Lisa!
杰西
Jesse.
很高兴你回来了  杰西
It's great to have you home again, Jess.
真不敢相信我能回来  我很高兴
I can't believe I'm going back. I'm glad.
- 太好了  - 我很高兴
- Good. - I'm glad.
- 祝你有愉快的一天  - 好的
- Have a good day, huh? - Okay.
谢谢妈妈
Thanks, Mom.
再见
Bye.
嗨
Hi.
什么事那么好笑
What is so funny?
那场派对非常好玩
That was a really great party.
- 谢谢你  莉莎  - 谢谢
- Thanks, Lise. - Thanks a lot.
我不敢相信这一切真的结束了
I can't believe it's actually all over.
- 我们不要再谈那件事了  - 好吧
- Let's not talk about it. - Okay.
- 哦 哈哈 - 这是?
- Ooh. Ha, ha. - Is this?
是我疯了  还是巴士开得太快
Am I going crazy or is this bus going too fast?
不会啊
It's going fine.
没问题
No problem.
不
No.
巴士开得太快了
This bus is going too fast.
- 莉莎  他开始加速了  - 没事的
- Lisa, it's starting to speed up. - It's fine.
没事的
It's fine.
司机
Driver.
- 司机  快停车  - 杰西  快坐下
- Driver, stop. - Jesse, just sit down.
对不起
I'm sorry.
没关系  没事的
It's okay. It's all right.
杰西  没事的
Jesse, it's okay.
一切都结束了
It's all over.